[{"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/犀牛_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/猫_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "0"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/犀牛_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "0"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/犀牛_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "1"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "0"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/猫_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "0"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "2"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "3"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/袋鼠_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "2"], ["2", "1"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/犀牛_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/猫_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "2"], ["2", "0"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狮子_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "3"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "2"], ["3", "1"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/猿猴_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}, {"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "0"], ["1", "1"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/长颈鹿_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/猫_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg", "num": "1", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "1", "num": "1", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "1"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "3"], ["3", "2"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}, {"body": [{"title": "连一连", "stem": "把同样多的动物用线连起来", "content": [[{"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg", "num": "2", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg", "num": "3", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg", "num": "4", "type": "img"}, {"val": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/猫_R1.svg", "num": "5", "type": "img"}], [{"val": "3", "num": "3", "type": "num"}, {"val": "4", "num": "4", "type": "num"}, {"val": "2", "num": "2", "type": "num"}, {"val": "5", "num": "5", "type": "num"}]], "type": "animal-connect"}], "answers": [["0", "2"], ["1", "0"], ["2", "1"], ["3", "3"]], "knowledges": ["5以内数的认识"], "resource": "", "type": "连线", "explain": "", "level": "1", "number": "1-1-3-05"}]